Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- H
  - Harris, Kathleen
  - Harris, Mark *
  - Harris, Pickens Elmer
  - Harris, Tracey A.
  - Harris, Verne
  - Harris, Walt
  - Harris-Schenz, Beverly
  - Harrison, C. Scott
  - Harrison, J. Ernest
  - Harrison, J. R.
  - Harrison, John Clement *
  - Harrison, Kathryn
  - Harrison, Lee
  - Harrison, Richard E.
  - Harrison, W. D. *
  - Harry, David, Jr.
  - Harry, Philip
  - Harshan, Michael H.
  - Hart, Antonio
  - Hart, Brian
  - Hart, David *
  - Hart, John L.
  - Hart, Melissa A.
  - Hart, Thomas A. (Dr.)
  - Hartje, Charles R.
  - Hartman, Cory
  - Hartman, Dawn
  - Hartman, Douglas K.
  - Hartman, Galen C.
  - Hartman, Richard T. *
  - Hartner, Miriam Sergay Sturgeon
  - Hartsock, James Harris
  - Hartwig, Charles C. "Doc"
  - Hartz, Mark
  - Harvey, George
  - Harvey, James White
  - Harvith, John D.
  - Hasch, David R.
  - Haselrig, Bruce
  - Haseltine, Benjamin, II *
  - Haseltine, Jack (Prof.)
  - Haskins, John
  - Hasselman, Carl
  - Hassouna, Wafih Ashraf (Dr.)
  - Hastings, Laura
  - Hatch, Orrin
  - Hatch, Theodore F. *
  - Hatfield, C. G.
  - Hatfull, Graham
  - Hathway, Marion *
  - Hatlestad, Wendy
  - Hattler, Brack
  - Haughton, Harvey J.
  - Haun, Ruth
  - Hausdorff, Henry (Dr.)
  - Hawk, Minor C. *
  - Hawker, James *
  - Hawkes, Robert W.
  - Hawkesworth, Alan S.
  - Hawkins, Alexander A.
  - Hawkins, Isaac
  - Hawkins, Mabel
  - Hawkins, Richard H.
  - Hay, Peter Heinrich
  - Hayashikawa, Doris *
  - Hayashi, T. Terry
  - Hayden, Carla
  - Hayden, Dianne
  - Hayden, Gary T.
  - Hayden, Ludwick
  - Hayden, Robert
  - Hayduk, Justin
  - Hayek, Fredrich A.
  - Hayes, Charles (Dr.)
  - Hayes, David
  - Hayes, Gerald
  - Hayes, Jack Patrick
  - Hayes, Tamia
  - Hays, Samuel P. *
  - Hays, William *
  - Haythorn, Samuel R.
  - Hazard, Cyril
  - Hazard, Leland
  - Hazlett, Lyle
  - Hazlett, William B.
  - Hazo, Robert
  - Hazo, Sam
  - Hazzard, Thomas T.
  - Head, Mike
  - Headlee, Drew
  - Healey, Joseph
  - Heaps, Willard "Bud"
  - Heard, James D., MD *
  - Hearn, Fil
  - Hearn, Millard F.
  - Hearne, J. J.
  - Heater, Michael G.
  - Heath, Brian R. G.
  - Heath, Edward Charles
  - Heath, Miah
  - Heath, S. Roy (Dr.) *
  - Heathers, Glen (Dr.)
  - Heaton, Lois
  - Hebda, Patricia A. *
  - Heberman, Ronald (Dr.)
  - Hebert, Delma Joseph
  - Hechelman, Herman W. *
  - Heckscher, William S.
  - Heckathorn, Stan
  - Hedden, M.
  - Heddleston, Bob *
  - Hedges, Joseph Edward *
  - Heesch, Christian M. (Dr.)
  - Hefferle, Ernest
  - Hefner, Jaye
  - Hegedus, Andrea H.
  - Heid, Omar Conrad
  - Heidt, Kathryn R.
  - Heimlich, Henry
  - Heinack, Eugene
  - Heiner, H. P.
  - Heinisch, Reinhard
  - Heins, Charles A.
  - Heinz, H. J.
  - Heinz, H. John, III
  - Heinz, Howard
  - Heinz, Margaret (Dr.)
  - Heinz, Vira I. (oversize) *
  - Heinze, Carl D.
  - Held, Julius
  - Held, Omar C. (oversize) *
  - Helfant, Reuben
  - Heller, Larry
  - Heller, Reinhold (Dr.)
  - Heller-LaBelle, Greg
  - Hellman, Arthur
  - Hellman, Helen *
  - Hemmy, Mary L. *
  - Hempel, Carl G. *
  - Hempel, John
  - Hemsley, Sherman
  - Hench, P. *
  - Henderliter, Charles
  - Henderson, Carlos
  - Henderson, David *
  - Henderson, Donald M. *
  - Henderson, John P.
  - Henderson, Peter
  - Henderson, Robert T.
  - Henderson, William F.
  - Hendler, Sandra
  - Hendrix, Roger W.
  - Hendy, Linda
  - Henker, Richard
  - Henniger, Trish Rau
  - Henninger, C. H.
  - Henninger, James M. (Dr.)
  - Hennings, Arthur G.
  - Henry, Blossom L. *
  - Henry, Elizabeth *
  - Henry, Leroy
  - Henry, M. Daniel
  - Henry, Richard J.
  - Henry, William L. *
  - Henshaw, Wandalie "Nancy"
  - Henson, Deborah M.
  - Heon, Sue
  - Hepburn, Hopewell *
  - Hepner, Fred
  - Hepple, Pamela
  - Herald, Charles W. *
  - Herberling, Richard (Dr.)
  - Herberman, Ronald
  - Herbert, D. J., Jr.
  - Hercules, David
  - Herman, Lawrence W.
  - Herndon, James H. *
  - Heron, Dwight
  - Herrero, Javier
  - Herring, David
  - Herron, Francis *
  - Herron, Samuel Parsons *
  - Hershberger, Pamela
  - Hershey, Nathan *
  - Hershl, Joyce
  - Hertz, Miriam
  - Hertzell, E. A.
  - Herzog, Joe
  - Heschel, Abraham Joshua
  - Hess, Melvin (Dr.)
  - Hesselbein, Frances
  - Herzberg, Frederick
  - Hetzel, Frederick A. *
  - Heugh, Hugh *
  - Heumann, Judith E.
  - Hewitt, Earle N., III
  - Hewitt, Vivian Davidson
  - Hexter, Robert
  - Heyward, Craig
  - Hibbitts, Bernard
  - Hickey, Beth
  - Hickey, Robert C. (oversize)
  - Hickman, William
  - Hicks, Bill
  - Hicks, Harold D.
  - Higbee, Edna Randall
  - Higgins, Harry
  - Higgins, T. F. X. *
  - Higgs, Russell
  - Higham, Keith
  - Highhill, Janet
  - Higie, William F.
  - Higinbotham, J. *
  - Higman, Henry Booth
  - Hilberg, Robert
  - Hill, Adrienne *
  - Hill, David G.
  - Hill, Edmund
  - Hill, Edwin H. *
  - Hill, John B.
  - Hill, J. T. (Colonel)
  - Hill, Lyndon Michael
  - Hill, Robert
  - Hill, Shirley
  - Hill, Warren *
  - Hillgrove, Bill
  - Hilliard, Jud
  - Hillier, Sharon
  - Hillman Family *
  - Hillman, Henry L. *
  - Hills, Erin
  - Hills, J. D. T.
  - Himes, William J.
  - Himmelhoch, Jonathan M. *
  - Hinchliffe, Joseph G. (Dr.)
  - Hincke, John I. (Colonel)
  - Hinderliter, Charles
  - Hines, Brian
  - Hines, Mary Christina
  - Hingson, Robert
  - Hinkel, Robert Dale *
  - Hinkley, John C.
  - Hinman, Robert
  - Hinton, Harold C. (Dr.)
  - Hinton, Joseph A.
  - Hippert, Christine
  - Hipple, John St. Clair
  - Hipwell, Richard M.
  - Hira, Ron
  - Hirsch, Barry E.
  - Hirsch, Raphael
  - Hirsch, William, Jr.
  - Hirst, Marian
  - Hirtle, Stephen
  - Hiser, P. J.
  - Hiserodt, John
  - Hite, Juliet Florine
  - Hjort, Elmer V.
  - Ho, Chien
  - Ho, Kong
  - Ho, Monto *
  - Hoadley, Mike
  - Hoagland, Tony
  - Hoare, Raymond R.
  - Hobson, Douglas
  - Hoch, David
  - Hoddie, James
  - Hodges, Fletcher, Jr. (oversize) *
  - Hodges, Margaret (oversize) *
  - Hodges, Richard *
  - Hodgkiss, Carol
  - Hodgson, Michael *
  - Hoelscher, Harold *
  - Hoelzeman, Ronald G.
  - Hoerr, John P.
  - Hofer, Jen
  - Hoffman, Carol
  - Hoffman, Eric P.
  - Hoffman, Frank N. *
  - Hoffman, George *
  - Hoffman, George W.
  - Hoffman, Gloria
  - Hoffman, James D. (Dr.)
  - Hoffman, Jonathan
  - Hoffman, Karen
  - Hoffman, Leslie
  - Hoffman, Rose Billie
  - Hofman, Klaus H. (oversize) *
  - Hogan, Jerry
  - Hogg, Francis N.
  - Hogg, Ira Dwight
  - Hogge, W. Allen
  - Hoke, Candice
  - Holahan, Francis *
  - Holahan, Mary
  - Holbay, Carol
  - Holbrook, Elmer Allen (oversize)
  - Holcomb, (Colonel)
  - Holden, Matthew (Dr.)
  - Holder, Gerald
  - Holdsworth, John Thom
  - Holland, Audrey
  - Holland, Frances
  - Holland, James
  - Holland, Peter
  - Holland, William Jacob
  - Hollander, Edward T.
  - Holliday, Malcolm A.
  - Hollingswarth, C. A.
  - Hollis, Benjamin (Lieutenant Colonel) *
  - Hollis, Clea P.
  - Hollis, Mark
  - Holloway, Randy
  - Holm, Margo B.
  - Holman, W. L.
  - Holmes, Jeremy
  - Holmok, Ernest *
  - Holstein, Martha
  - Holstein, Theodore
  - Holt, Nancy
  - Holtz, Dolores
  - Holtz, John
  - Holzner, Burkart
  - Holzer, Carolyn
  - Holzinger, Elmer J.
  - Holzman, Albert G. *
  - Honath, Kim
  - Hommel, Beth
  - Hondros, Chris
  - Hooker, Clifford *
  - Hooker, Davenport *
  - Hooker, Elbert L.
  - Hoon, Merle R.
  - Hoop, George A.
  - Hoopes, David S.
  - Hoover, Edgar M. *
  - Hope, Richard (oversize) *
  - Hopewell, Hepburn *
  - Hopkins, Andrew
  - Hopkins, Benjamin B.
  - Hopkins, Jo Ann
  - Hopkins, John Henry *
  - Hopkins, Michael D.
  - Hopper, Sarah *
  - Hopper-Scherch, Shirlee
  - Hora, Galen F. (Rev.)
  - Hord, Earl F.
  - Horgan, Chuck
  - Horgan, John J.
  - Horn, John
  - Horn, Michael *
  - Horn, Thomas L., MD
  - Horne, Lisa
  - Horner, Clyde
  - Horner, Douglas J.
  - Horner, Jocelyn
  - Hornbostel, Henry
  - Hornsby, Matt
  - Horoho, Patricia
  - Horowitz, Howard
  - Horowitz, Mara
  - Horowitz, Michael
  - Horowitz, Norman H.
  - Horowitz, Tamara
  - Horrocks, Norman *
  - Horton, John A., III
  - Horstmann, John Paul
  - Horty, John *
  - Hortz, John F.
  - Horwitz, Solis *
  - Hosack, Ivan *
  - Hosick, William LeRoy *
  - Hough, Howard E.
  - Hough, Rex
  - Houghton, Gerald
  - Houk, Kendall N.
  - Houle, Cyril O. *
  - Hountras, Peter T.
  - Houston, David
  - Hout, Mariah
  - Hovde, B. J.
  - Hovey, Bertram
  - Hovey, Walter
  - Howald, A. M. *
  - Howar, Donald
  - Howard, Carrie
  - Howard, James J.
  - Howard, John A. *
  - Howard, John Tasker *
  - Howard, Lawrence *
  - Howarth, Herbert *
  - Howarth, Walter O. *
  - Howe, Gloria
  - Howe, Thomas M. *
  - Hower, Donal E.
  - Howie, Edmund *
  - Howland, Ben
  - Howland, Harold
  - Howland, Robert H.
  - Howze, Sam
  - Hoyaux, Max F.
  - Hoye, Thomas
  - Hoyt, Dale
  - Hrapchak, Evelyn
  - Hsia, Chih-Tsing *
  - Hsieh, Margaret
  - Hsieh, Chiao-Min "Jimmy" *
  - Hsu, Cho-Yun
  - Hsu, C. Y.
  - Hsu, Tse-Chi
  - Huang, Leaf
  - Huang, Xiang
  - Huang, Xiaoli
  - Huard, Johnny
  - Hubbard, Rebecca
  - Hubbuch, Leo P.
  - Hubel, Carl A.
  - Huber, George A.
  - Hubin, Donald
  - Huckenberg, George R. *
  - Hudac, Damon
  - Hudson, Jesse T., Jr. *
  - Hudson, Yvonne
  - Huey, Edmund Burke
  - Huff, Tom *
  - Huffman, Carrie *
  - Huffman, Mona L.
  - Hufnagel, James A.
  - Huggins, Raleigh R. (Dr.) *
  - Hughes, Bill
  - Hughes, Brooke
  - Hughes, Donovan
  - Hughes, Joh W.
  - Hughes, Peter M. *
  - Hughes, Russell
  - Hughes, Ryan D.
  - Hughes, Sallie
  - Hughey, Andrew
  - Hughey, Rebecca P.
  - Hull, Glynda A.
  - Hulpa, Kelly
  - Humanic, Thomas J.
  - Hume, Ruth
  - Humes, Theodore
  - Hummel, Lani
  - Hummel, Ray *
  - Hummon, Norman (Dr.) *
  - Humphrey, Allen L. *
  - Humphrey, Kathy
  - Humphrey, Tryphena *
  - Humphries, Frederick
  - Huneke, Richard B.
  - Hung, Tin-Kan
  - Hung, William
  - Hunia, Edward M.
  - Hunkele, Catherine, PhD
  - Hunker, Henry Louis
  - Hunt, Charles W.
  - Hunt, Joseph McVicker
  - Hunt, Percival *
  - Hunt, Richard N.
  - Hunt, Susan
  - Hunter, Alexander S.
  - Hunter, Beverly J.
  - Hunter, Charlene
  - Hunter, J. Stewart
  - Hunter, James *
  - Hunter, Ralph W. *
  - Hunting, Eugene *
  - Huntley, Louis Crow
  - Hupchick, Dennis P. *
  - Hurrell, A. S.
  - Hurwitz, Dennis (Dr.)
  - Hussan, Abul
  - Hussey, L. Thomas
  - Husted, Steve
  - Huston, McCready
  - Hutchinson, Donald
  - Hutchisson, Elmer (oversize) *
  - Hutelmyer, Andrew P.
  - Hutson, Percival
  - Hwang, Charles
  - Hydovitz, Jerrold D.
- I
  - Iacoangllo, John Paul
  - Iacono, Aldo T.
  - Iannarelli, Cynthia L.
  - Ianni, Karen F.
  - Iddriss, Adam
  - Idzkowsky, Henry J.
  - Ildstad, Suzanne T.
  - Imber, Stanley Donald
  - Immroth, John Phillip
  - Infanti, Anthony C.
  - Inga, Juan
  - Inglis, D. R.
  - Inman, J. Jeffrey
  - Innocenti, John
  - Ireland, Don
  - Irgang, Paul
  - Irish, R. E.
  - Irrgang, James
  - Irvin, Matt
  - Irvine, Emily G. *
  - Irvine, Peter B.
  - Irvis, K. Leroy *
  - Irwin, Laurence E. *
  - Isaacs, Asher *
  - Isaacs, Nathan
  - Ishikawa, Mamoru
  - Isler, Charles *
  - Ismail, Noor
  - Ismail, Y. H.
  - Isenberg, Robert
  - Isner, Dale *
  - Itter, William Martin
  - Iverson, Jana
  - Iyengar, Satish
- J
  - Jablonski, Stanley F. *
  - Jackson, Beryl B. Haughton
  - Jackson, Chevalier
  - Jackson, Jesse (Rev.)
  - Jackson, John H. (Rev.)
  - Jackson, Mark
  - Jackson, Petrina D.
  - Jackson, Tyron
  - Jackson, William V.
  - Jacob, F. M.
  - Jacob, Herbert
  - Jacob, Theodore
  - Jacobs, Samuel (Dr.)
  - Jacobs, William R.
  - Jacobsen, Einar William
  - Jacobson, Lewis
  - Jacoby, George
  - Jaeckel, Hugo
  - Jafarian, Dana
  - Jaffe, Lois *
  - Jaher, Frederick
  - Jai, Janet J.
  - Jakicic, John
  - Jakubowski, Janet
  - Jalbert, Russell R. *
  - Jamar, Idorenyin
  - James, Alfred Proctor (oversize) *
  - James, Dorothy Batchelor
  - James, Eric *
  - James, Jean
  - James, Joseph A. *
  - Jameson, Nora
  - Jameson, Storm
  - Jamieson, Edith
  - Jamison, Auleene Marley (oversize) *
  - Janecka, Ivo P. *
  - Janjic, Jelena M.
  - Janis, Allen L. (Dr.)
  - Jannetta, Pete J.
  - Januzzi, Gilberto
  - Jarrett, Thomas M. *
  - Jasnow, David
  - Jaszczun, Wasyl *
  - Jaynes, Oval
  - Jazzam, Joseph (Dr.) *
  - Jeffers, Robinson "John"
  - Jefferson, Blanche *
  - Jefferson, Francine
  - Jeffrey, Arthur
  - Jeffrey, George A. *
  - Jeffreys, Jack
  - Jeffries, Jay
  - Jegasothy, Brian *
  - Jen-Jacobson, Linda
  - Jenkins, Dan
  - Jenkins, Delanie
  - Jenkins, John
  - Jenkins, Maureen
  - Jenkinson, Dave
  - Jenness, John L.
  - Jennings, J. Richard
  - Jennings, James W.
  - Jennings, Otto E. *
  - Jennings, Rashad
  - Jenny, Florence Stephante
  - Jerebko, Peter
  - Jerne, Neils (Dr.)
  - Jerrell, S. Lee
  - Jesko, Chad
  - Jett, Willie
  - Jewell, Richard G.
  - Jewell, Richard J.
  - Jian, Yu
  - Jillson, B. C.
  - Jiminez, Michael F.
  - Jobusch, Wallace E.
  - Johanson, Sue
  - Johns, Elizabeth
  - Johns, Lee
  - Johns, Robert M.
  - Johnson, B. Delia
  - Johnson, Bob (SEE Johnson, Robert)
  - Johnson, Branden
  - Johnson, Bruce A.
  - Johnson, Bryan
  - Johnson, Candace S.
  - Johnson, Carl
  - Johnson, Chad
  - Johnson, C. M.
  - Johnson, Dan
  - Johnson, Delores E.
  - Johnson, Edward S. (oversize) *
  - Johnson, Gary
  - Johnson, Glen
  - Johnson, H. M.
  - Johnson, Hazel M.
  - Johnson, J. Karl
  - Johnson, Jon
  - Johnson, Jonas T. *
  - Johnson, Joseph E. (Dr.)
  - Johnson, Jotham
  - Johnson, K. Jeffrey *
  - Johnson, K.
  - Johnson, Kevin
  - Johnson, Kjel A.
  - Johnson, L. Samuel
  - Johnson, Larry D.
  - Johnson, Reginald H. (oversize) *
  - Johnson, Robert (oversize)
  - Johnson, Robert *
  - Johnson, Ronald C.
  - Johnson, Roswell Hill
  - Johnson, S. Harris *
  - Johnson, Samuel L.
  - Johnson, Sharon
  - Johnson, Sharon (oversize)
  - Johnson, William H. E. *
  - Johnston, Alex *
  - Johnston, Hank
  - Johnston, James I.
  - Johnston, James R.
  - Johnston, Jamie
  - Johnston, Jenn
  - Johnston, Louis W. H.
  - Johnston, Michele
  - Johnston, William A.
  - Johnston, William M.
  - Johnston, Zoe Allison
  - Jollie, Malcolm T.
  - Jonas, Klaus (Dr.) *
  - Jones, Alex K.
  - Jones, Ann
  - Jones, Andrew
  - Jones, Austin *
  - Jones, Bill
  - Jones, Bobby
  - Jones, Bruce A.
  - Jones, C. Christy
  - Jones, Charles L.
  - Jones, Charles O. *
  - Jones, Christian
  - Jones, Chuck
  - Jones, Clement Russell
  - Jones, Daub *
  - Jones, David A.
  - Jones, Donald H.
  - Jones, Frank V.
  - Jones, Frank Walter *
  - Jones, George
  - Jones, George McMaster
  - Jones, Gordon
  - Jones, Harold
  - Jones, Hilda *
  - Jones, John W. *
  - Jones, Mildred
  - Jones, Miles H.
  - Jones, Montfort *
  - Jones, Nicholas F.
  - Jones, Paulette
  - Jones, Putnam Fennell (oversize) *
  - Jones, Ray
  - Jones, Rosalynd
  - Jones, Russell
  - Jones, Ruth
  - Jones, W. D. *
  - Jonnet, Margaret L.
  - Jordan, Billy Joe
  - Jordan, Christine *
  - Jordan, Frank Craig
  - Jordan, Kenneth
  - Jordan, Maureen
  - Jordan, Raymond E.
  - Jordan, Sandra
  - Jordano, Joe
  - Josey, E. J. *
  - Joshi, James
  - Jovin, Tudor
  - Joyce, Robert *
  - Judson, William D.
  - Judy, Ronald
  - Juffs, Alan
  - Juhl, Randy *
  - Julian, Dean
  - Julian, Thomas B. *
  - Jung, Richard (Dr.)
  - Junreis, Charles
  - Junker, Buford H.
  - Juranko, John A.
  - Jurisic, Pedja
  - Jury, Bob
  - Justice, Amy
- K
  - Kadec, Sarah T.
  - Kaelin, Elmer
  - Kafka, Folke
  - Kagan, Shelly
  - Kagel, John H.
  - Kaguyutan, Matthew
  - Kahl, Hugo
  - Kaktins, Uldis
  - Kaliden, William *
  - Kalnicki, Shalom *
  - Kamarck, Tom
  - Kamboh, M. Ilyas
  - Kameen, Paul
  - Kamenva, Marina
  - Kamerer, Donald B. *
  - Kaminski, Naftali
  - Kammer, Adolph G. (Dr.)
  - Kammer, Glenn D.
  - Kamon, Eliezer
  - Kampmeier, Otto F.
  - Kampmeyer, P. M. (oversize) *
  - Kanal, Emanuel
  - Kandler, Karl
  - Kane, Eileen
  - Kane, Howard L.
  - Kane, Paula
  - Kane, Sandra L.
  - Kane, Thomas
  - Kanefsky, Morton (Dr.) *
  - Kang, Jim
  - Kang, Young Woo
  - Kaniecki, Robert
  - Kansky, Karel
  - Kanter, Steven
  - Kapa, Steve
  - Kapelka, Lester E. *
  - Kaplan, Barry
  - Kaplan, Mark
  - Kappel, Felice A.
  - Karapinka, Orysia
  - Karcher, Ken
  - Karelitz, Edwin
  - Karimi, Hassan
  - Karioki, James
  - Karn, Harry W.
  - Karns, George M.
  - Karo, Aaron
  - Karol, Meryl H.
  - Karp, Richard
  - Karpf, Michael *
  - Karpinski, Marek
  - Karsten, Peter *
  - Karzel, Helmut (Dr.) *
  - Kasica, Marianne
  - Kasper, Nancy
  - Kasperko, Jean M.
  - Kassem, Bachar
  - Kasten, Jack
  - Kaszycki, Emily
  - Katchadourian, Haig
  - Katkowski, Michelle
  - Katsoyannis, Panayotis G. (Dr.) *
  - Katz, Arnold
  - Katz, Joseph M.
  - Katz, Leo
  - Katz, Leon
  - Katz, Lynn F.
  - Katz, Lynn S.
  - Katz, Saul Milton *
  - Katz, Stephen
  - Kauffman, Robert
  - Kaufman, Frederick *
  - Kaufman, Larry J. *
  - Kaufman, Oxanna Rentler
  - Kaufman, Terence
  - Kaufmann, Emma
  - Kaun, David E.
  - Kay, Carol
  - Kaye, Walter
  - Kearns, Kevin P.
  - Kearns, John
  - Kearney, Hugh F. *
  - Kearney, Walter A.
  - Keder, Wilbert E.
  - Keefe, William J. *
  - Keeler, Henry Bowman
  - Keeler, James E. *
  - Keeler, John T. S.
  - Keeler, Larry W.
  - Keenan, Tanya
  - Keeton, David G. *
  - Keeve, J. Philip
  - Keffer, Frederic
  - Kehl, James
  - Kehl, William B. *
  - Kelper, R. Kenneth
  - Keith, Harold L.
  - Keith, Ruth
  - Kelleher, Kelly J.
  - Keller, Lawrence W.
  - Keller, William
  - Kelley, David E.
  - Kellman, Amy
  - Kellum, John
  - Kelly, Andrew Jackson, Jr.
  - Kelly, Brian
  - Kelly, Fred
  - Kelly, Gene *
  - Kelly, George A. *
  - Kelly, James *
  - Kelly, William C. (Dr.) *
  - Kemerer, Chris
  - Kendall, Leyon
  - Keniston, Hayward (Dr.) *
  - Kennah, H. Edwin
  - Kennard, Edward A. *
  - Kennard, William J.
  - Kennedy, Dennis
  - Kennedy, John
  - Kennedy, Rhett F.
  - Kennedy, Roland *
  - Kennedy, Thomas
  - Kent, Allen *
  - Kent, Allen (Time Capsule) *
  - Kerber, Charles (Dr.)
  - Keres, Lois *
  - Kerr, B. *
  - Kerr, C. U.
  - Kerr, David R. *
  - Kerr, Hugh Thomson
  - Kerr, Joseph Reynolds (Rev.) *
  - Kerr, Mary
  - Kerr, Samuel R. *
  - Kerr, Thomas B. *
  - Kertesz, Andrew E. (Dr.) *
  - Kesler, C. C.
  - Kessler, Aharon
  - Kestler, Hal C. *
  - Ketchen, Kenney
  - Ketchum, Carlton
  - Kettain, M. A.
  - Khachaturian, Zaren S.
  - Khalouf, Fred *
  - Khan, Abdul G. *
  - Khan, Oliver
  - Khan, Saleem
  - Khatchadorrian, Haig (Dr.) *
  - Khine-Hackett, Rose
  - Khonsari, Michael M.
  - Khoury, S. G.
  - Khurana, R. C.
  - Kidd, Howard C. *
  - Kidney, Walter C.
  - Kierman, Joseph F., Jr.
  - Kiesewetter, William (Dr.)
  - Kiesling, Scott
  - Kiewiet-DeJonge, Joost
  - Kilmann, Ralph *
  - Kilpatrick, Lori
  - Kilpatrick, Stephen
  - Kim, Chai
  - Kim, Hakjoon
  - Kim, Hong-Koo
  - Kim, Joo Han
  - Kim, Master Kyuaha
  - Kim, Sung-Hou
  - Kimbo, Conney M. *
  - Kimmel, Elaine
  - Kimmel, Margaret Mary *
  - Kincaid, Latoya
  - Kinder, Chuck
  - Kindle, William D.
  - Kindlin, Jean
  - Kiner, George M.
  - King, Charles Glen (oversize) *
  - King, Cyrus B.
  - King, Frances B.
  - King, H. E. (Dr.) *
  - King, Josiah
  - King, Kim
  - King, Linda
  - King, Mark
  - King, Maxwell
  - King, Paul M.
  - King, Ray
  - King, Wendy
  - King, William R. *
  - Kingdom, Roger (oversize) *
  - Kingsley, Lawrence
  - Kingston, Maxine Hong
  - Kinnan, Cynthia
  - Kinnard, Ed *
  - Kinne, Emma *
  - Kinnell, Galway
  - Kinsay, Susan
  - Kintner, Elizabeth
  - Kintner, Samuel M. *
  - Kip, Kevin E.
  - Kipp, H. A.
  - Kirby, Daria
  - Kirby, Robert E.
  - Kirby, Woodrow, Jr.
  - Kirimi, Bulent *
  - Kirimi, Hassan
  - Kirisci, Levent
  - Kirk, George M.
  - Kirkley, Raymond
  - Kirksey, Larry
  - Kirkwood, John M.
  - Kirtane, Jayant
  - Kiselev, Alexey A.
  - Kish, Gabor
  - Kisiel, Chester C.
  - Kiskadden, Margaret
  - Kispert, Paul H. *
  - Kissane, Dennis
  - Kissell, Fred
  - Kissell, Joseph C.
  - Kissinger, Henry *
  - Kita, Sandy
  - Kitanc, Hiroaki
  - Kitson, Herbert W.
  - Kitzes, Esther *
  - Kjeldergaard, Paul M.
  - Klages, Chester
  - Klarlund, Jes K.
  - Klein, Alan F.
  - Klein, Arnold
  - Klein, Elizabeth
  - Klein, George de Vries
  - Klein, Roger
  - Klein, William
  - Kleinman, Edward A.
  - Kleist, Virginia
  - Klemanski, Cynthia
  - Klemek, Joel
  - Klimcheck, Albert A. *
  - Kline, Caryl *
  - Kline, H. V. B. and Mrs. *
  - Kline, Susan
  - Klinge, John M.
  - Klingensmith, James M.
  - Klinzing, George E.
  - Klionsky, Bernard
  - Klob, R. E. *
  - Klopfer, Lepold E.
  - Klotz, Oscar
  - Klucevsek, Guy *
  - Knapp, Amy
  - Knapp, James
  - Knapp, Janet
  - Knecht, Laura
  - Knigge, Karl M.
  - Knight, Brandin
  - Knight, Bryan
  - Knight, Tiffany
  - Knights, Lionel Charles *
  - Knipp, John
  - Kniseley, Ralph
  - Knobil, Ernst
  - Knoer, William
  - Knoles, Charles
  - Knoll, Catherine Baker
  - Knolle, Laurence M.
  - Knopfel, Willy F.
  - Knowles, Morris
  - Knox, Helen
  - Knox, James
  - Knox, Jane Eleanor
  - Knudsen, John K.
  - Kobayashi, Kazuo
  - Kobosky, Bernard J. *
  - Kobulnicky, Paul
  - Koch, Julius A. *
  - Koch, Philip
  - Koch, Robert W. *
  - Kochanek, Patrick *
  - Kocher, Frederick L.
  - Kocher, Matt
  - Kochik, John M. *
  - Kockelmans, Joseph J.
  - Kodlin, Dankward (Dr.)
  - Koehler, Ludmilla
  - Koehler, Martha
  - Koehler, Norman
  - Koehler, Peter
  - Koehler, Richard David
  - Koehler, Steve
  - Koenig, Adolph *
  - Koenig, Donna
  - Koenig, Henry Titus *
  - Koerner, Henry
  - Koeske, Rand
  - Kogut, Leonard
  - Kohberger, Clint *
  - Kohberger, Paul B. *
  - Kohler, Victor
  - Kohler, Vincent
  - Kohutiak, Ulana
  - Koide, Kazunon
  - Kolar, Michael
  - Kolar, Patricia
  - Kolbert, Jack
  - Koleda, Michael S. *
  - Kolish, Kate
  - Kollinger, John P.
  - Kolko, David
  - Kolls, Jay K.
  - Koloc, Fred
  - Komariah, Enis
  - Komichak, Michael
  - Komlos, John
  - Kondis, Stephen *
  - Kondziolka, Douglas
  - Kong, Nan
  - Koniak, Susan P.
  - Koperek, Bernard P. *
  - Kopp, Drew
  - Korb, Lawrence
  - Korbitz, W. E. *
  - Koretsky, Alan
  - Korfhage, Robert R.
  - Korman, David
  - Kormos, Robert L. *
  - Kornblith, Paul L.
  - Kornick, Kenneth M.
  - Koros, A. M. C.
  - Korth, Willard William
  - Kory, William
  - Koskoff, David
  - Koslow, Joseph
  - Kosoladolkitt, Yawvaluck
  - Kosowsky, Arthur
  - Kothari, Geeta
  - Kotlowitz, Alex
  - Kotkiewicz, Adam
  - Kovach, Carol *
  - Kovacs, Alberta R.
  - Kovak, Albert J.
  - Kovalcik, Gena
  - Kovaos, Elmer C.
  - Kowalczyk, Donna L.
  - Kozamek, Carlos
  - Kozikowski, Alan P.
  - Kozikowski, Mitchell
  - Kozlol, Stephen M., Jr.
  - Kraemer, Keven L.
  - Krafcik, Patricia
  - Kramer, David
  - Kramer, Harry A. *
  - Kramer, Martin
  - Kramer, Mary Albert (Sister)
  - Kramer, Saul
  - Kramer, Vida Demas *
  - Krammer, Adolph
  - Kraus, Bertram S. (Dr.)
  - Krauser, Carl
  - Kraut, Alan
  - Kraut, Robert
  - Kraynek, William T.
  - Krebs, Walter
  - Kreiling, Delia A.
  - Kreit, John W.
  - Kreithen, Mel (Dr.)
  - Krenzelok, Edward P.
  - Krich, Cynthia
  - Krieg, C. G.
  - Krieg, William J.
  - Krieger, Alexander
  - Krieger, Frederick
  - Krikorian, Mike
  - Kril, Olga
  - Kriley, Charity
  - Krimer, Leonid S.
  - Krips, Henry
  - Krips, Valerie
  - Krishnaiah, P. R.
  - Krishnamurthy, Pershant
  - Krishtalka, Leonard
  - Kriska, Andrea
  - Kristiansen, James
  - Krithen, Melvin L.
  - Kroboth, Frank J. *
  - Kroboth, Patricia
  - Kroeger, Hilda H.
  - Kroh, Dean (Dr.)
  - Kronenberg, Philip
  - Kroon, Alice Benson
  - Krueger, Robert Otto
  - Kruman, Susan G.
  - Kruper, Donald C. *
  - Kruse, Theophile K.
  - Krutzsch, Philip (Dr.)
  - Krynski, Magnus J.
  - Ksanznak, Jessie
  - Kuebel, Alice
  - Kuehn, Ruth P. *
  - Kuehner, H. G.
  - Kuhn, J. Craig
  - Kuhtile, Nellie Jewel
  - Kuller, Lewis
  - Kumar, Anu
  - Kumar, Shankar
  - Kummer, Gertrude
  - Kunich, Amy
  - Kunig, Horst F.
  - Kunstler, James Howard